http://www.gliffy.com/privacy-policy

Gliffy Privacy Policy | Gliffy
Skip to main content
Main navigationProductsGliffy's Atlassian AppsGliffy OnlineSolutionsDiagrams for BusinessesDiagrams for Software EngineeringDiagrams for Design ProjectsResourcesResources Featured LinksResourcesFind helpful articles, papers, videos, and more from our seasoned experts.Resources LinksResources RowPapers & VideosBlogCase StudiesSupportSupport Featured LinksSupportWe're here for you! Browse our guides or talk to our team.Support LinksSupport Links RowSupport OverviewDocumentationPartnersFree TrialCreated with Avocode.SearchSecondary NavigationPricingBlogCompanyAbout Gliffy by PerforceCareers at PerforcePartnersContact UsLoginGliffyMain Navigation - Mega MenuProductsMain Navigation - Mega MenuGliffy's Atlassian AppsBuilt for Software Developers, Perfected for Any Team in the Atlassian EcosystemGliffy OnlineDrag and Drop Diagramming. Capture and Share Your Ideas in Just a Few ClicksSolutionsMain Navigation - Mega MenuDiagrams for BusinessesDiagrams for Design ProjectsDiagrams for Software EngineeringResourcesMain Navigation - Mega MenuExplore ResourcesPapers & VideosCase StudiesBlogCompare Diagramming SoftwareRead NowSupportMain Navigation - Mega MenuSupport OverviewDocumentationContact SupportUser ManualsSupport DeskBrowse our guides or talk to our team.Explore SupportPartnersFree TrialPricingBlogCompanyMain Navigation - Mega MenuAbout Gliffy by PerforceCareers at PerforceContact UsPartnersLoginGliffy Privacy PolicyGliffy Privacy PolicyCopyright InfringementTerms of UseEULA for Atlassian PluginsContact UsContact UsPrivacy PolicyThis privacy statement ("Privacy Policy") covers the website www.Gliffy.com, owned and operated by Gliffy, Inc. ("Gliffy", "we", "us", "our") and the products and services Gliffy provides. Gliffy knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. By visiting the Gliffy website, submitting information or using any of our products or services, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?This Privacy Policy covers Gliffy's treatment of personal information that Gliffy gathers when you are on the Gliffy website and when you use Gliffy services. Also, this Privacy Policy covers Gliffy's treatment of any personal information that Gliffy's business partners share with Gliffy. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Gliffy does not own or control, or to individuals that Gliffy does not employ or manage.What Personal Information About Users Does Gliffy Collect?Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to personalize and improve our service. We collect the following types of information from our users:1. Information You Provide to Us:We may receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. The personal information you provide may be used for such purposes as responding to your requests for certain products and services, customizing the advertising and content you see, communicating with you about specials, sales offers and new products, and improving our products and services.We may collect such information from you by the following means:Registration: In order for you to use our website, you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we require your email address.Gliffy Premium: To process your order for Gliffy Premium, we require contact information (such as billing address) and PayPal information. This information is used for billing purposes.Feedback: You may accept our invitation to provide feedback or participate in surveys for our research purposes, including providing screenshots of how you use the Gliffy services.2. Automatic Information:We may receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Gliffy may automatically receive and record certain "traffic data" on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Gliffy cookie information, and the page you requested. Gliffy uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its server, analyze trends and administer the website.Generally, our service may automatically collect usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our website and its components. This data is only used in the aggregate, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of collective data enables us to figure out how often users use parts of the website, so we can make the website appealing to as many users as possible. In addition, we may provide statistical information, not information about you personally, to our partners about how our users, collectively, use our website. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use their areas and our website, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal Web experience.Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While Gliffy will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.3. E-mail Communications:We may receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail from Gliffy if your computer supports this type of program, in order to help us make e-mails more interesting and helpful. We may also send out emails with news or promotions. If you do not want to receive e-email or other mail from us, please update your profile under the "Profile" section of the website.4. Information from Other Sources:For purposes such as improving personalization of our service, we may receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.What About Cookies?Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we may transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. Gliffy cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your email address is.The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of Gliffy's most attractive features.Some of our business partners may use cookies on our website (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.Will Gliffy Share Any of the Information it Receives?We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. We share your personal information only with your consent or to the business partners and affiliates as described below:Affiliated Business We Do Not Control:We are affiliated with a variety of businesses and work closely with them. You can easily recognize when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction. We will only share personal information that is necessary for the affiliate to complete the transaction. We require our affiliates to provide the same level of privacy protection that we do and they do not have the right to share or use personal information for any purpose other than for an authorized transaction.Personnel:Our personnel (including, for the avoidance of doubt, consultants and/or contractors) may have access to user information while carrying out their duties in the normal course of our company business.Agents:We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples include fulfilling orders, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, collecting and analyzing data relating to your visit to our website, providing marketing assistance, processing payments, and providing customer service. You hereby consent to our sharing of your personal information for the above purposes.We utilize the following Google Analytics Features to help us collect and analyze data related to your visit to our website such as page views and average time on page:Demographics and Interests ReportingRemarketing with Google AnalyticsWe may use this data with third-party cookies such as Adroll and Adwords Remarketing to later serve targeted display banners or text ads to you on the Google Display Network and other ad exchanges such as Facebook.You may opt out of the Google Analytics Features by following the instructions in the following link: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/We may also utilize various analytical tools to track how you interact with the Gliffy website and services. We change such analytical tools from time to time, but as of the date this Privacy Policy was last revised, these analytical tools included Mixpanel (https://mixpanel.com), Amplitude (https://amplitude.com), Marketo (https://www.marketo.com) and Hubspot (https://www.hubspot.com). Such analytical tools may allow us to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking). Please note that we do not respond to or honor “do not track” signals or similar mechanisms transmitted by web browsers.This website uses the Lucky Orange analytics system to help improve usability and the customer experience. Lucky Orange may record mouse clicks, mouse movements and scrolling activity. Lucky Orange does not track this activity on any site that does not use the Lucky Orange system. You can choose to disable the Lucky Orange system at http://www.luckyorange.com/disable.php.We use a third party payment processor to process payments made to us. In connection with the processing of such payments, we do not retain any personally identifiable information or any financial information such as credit card numbers. Rather, all such information is provided directly to our third party processor, Stripe, whose use of your personal information is governed by their privacy policy, which may be viewed at https://stripe.com/us/privacy.Promotional Offers:We may send offers to certain users on behalf of other businesses. However, when we do so, we do not give the other business your name and address. If you do not wish to receive these offers, please update your profile under the "Profile" section of the website.Business Transfers:In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Gliffy, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party.Protection of Gliffy and Others:We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Gliffy, our employees, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.Is Information About Me Secure?Gliffy has implemented technical and organizational measures, appropriate to the risk, to protect your personal information against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss or alteration and unauthorized disclosure or access. However, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information provided online.Your Gliffy account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to work to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer.We use industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software to protect the security of your personal information during transmission, which encrypts all of the information you input.Only Gliffy employees who need personal information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to it. All of our employees are trained and kept up to date on our privacy and security practices.How Long Does Gliffy Retain My Information?Gliffy retains the personal information that we collect about you for as long as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We also may retain your personal information for a longer period of time on the basis of our legitimate interests in providing or marketing our services to you or as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes, and to enforce our agreements. Even if we delete some or all of your personal information, we may continue to retain and use information that has been aggregated or anonymized so that it can no longer be used for personal identification.What Information Can I Access?You can access your personal information on our website and correct, amend, or delete information that is inaccurate by updating your profile under the "Profile" section of the website.What Choices Do I Have?As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, but then you may be unable to use certain features on our website.You are able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those listed in the "What Personal Information About Users Does Gliffy Collect?" section above. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records.You may request deletion of your Gliffy account by sending an email to contacting us at our support page. Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account.If you do not wish to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please update your profile under the "Profile" section of the website. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Gliffy website, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.As explained earlier, the "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. Please note, however, that if your browser does not accept cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of some of our attractive features.Can Children Use Gliffy's Services?You must be 18 years and older to register to use the Gliffy website. As a result, Gliffy does not specifically collect information about children.Additional European Union Privacy RightsIf you are a resident of the European Union, you have certain rights with respect to your personal information under the General Data Protection Regulation (Regulation (EU) 2016/679) (the “GDPR”), including the following:The right of access to your personal information.The right to rectify your personal information if it is incorrect or incomplete.The right to have your personal information erased (“right to be forgotten”) if certain grounds are met.The right to withdraw your consent to our processing of your personal information at any time (if our processing is based on consent).The right to object to our processing of your personal information (if processing is based on legitimate interests).The right to object to our processing of your personal information for direct marketing purposes.The right to receive your personal information from us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, and the right to transmit your personal information to another controller without hindrance from us (data portability).You may contact us at support(at)gliffy(dot)com to exercise any of the above rights. We may request specific information from you to confirm your identity, and in some circumstances we may charge a reasonable fee for access to your personal information. Furthermore, if you believe that our processing of your personal information is inconsistent with your data protection rights under the GDPR and we have not adequately addressed your concerns, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the data protection supervisory authority of your country.Conditions of UseIf you decide to visit the Gliffy website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.Third Party WebsitesGliffy services may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the Gliffy website. These other websites are not under Gliffy control. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from the Gliffy website are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and Gliffy is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.Changes to this Privacy PolicyGliffy may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Gliffy website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.Questions or ConcernsIf you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at the Gliffy website, please send a detailed message to support(at)gliffy(dot)com. Your privacy is important to us and we will make every effort to resolve your concerns.Effective Date of This Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy was last revised on May 11, 2018.Footer menuProductsGliffy's Atlassian AppsGliffy OnlineSolutionsDiagrams for BusinessesDiagrams for Design ProjectsDiagrams for Software EngineeringResourcesBlogPapers & VideosCase StudiesSupportDocumentationFAQGliffy Diagram for ConfluenceGliffy Diagram for JIRAGliffy DiagramCompanyAbout Gliffy by PerforceCareers at PerforcePartners	ContactContact UsRequest SupportPartnersPartners PortalQuick LinksFree TrialPricingLoginGliffy by Perforce © 2020 Perforce Software, Inc.Terms of Use  |  Privacy Policy | SitemapSocial MenuFacebookTwitterLinkedInYoutubeRSS
